Council on Wage and Price Stability Newsletters and Releases 5207
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Council on Wage and Price Stability Newsletters and Releases
1976-1980
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Council on Wage and Price Stability
5207
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Press releases, reports, publications.
Press releases and newsletters of the United States Council on Wage and Price Stability.
5621148
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 24, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 06, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Wage-price policy -- United States; Inflation (Finance) -- United States; United States. Council on Wage and Price Stability (U.S.)
5621148
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  June 1976
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  July 1976
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  August 1976
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  September 1976
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  October 1976
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  November 1976
- Press Releases, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  December 1976
- Staff Report, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Press Releases, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  January 1977
- Press Releases, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  February 1977
- Press Releases, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  March 1977
- Press Releases, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  April 1977
- Press Releases, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  May 1977
- Executive Office of the President News, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  June 1977
- Executive Office of the President News, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  July 1977
- Executive Office of the President News, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  August 1977
- Executive Office of the President News, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  October 1977
- Executive Office of the President News, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  November 1977
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  January 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  March 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  April 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  May 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  June 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  July 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  August 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  September 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  October 1978
- Executive Office of the President News, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  November 1979
- Executive Office of the President News, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  June 1980